Some gifts come in extraordinary packages.
Like Sunday, Like Rain is a drama, music film directed by Frank Whaley.
A struggling musician becomes a 12-year-old musical
prodigy's guardian for a summer.
Eleanor, played by Leighton Meester.
Barbara, played by Debra Messing.
Dennis, played by Billie Joe Armstrong.
Reggie, played by Julian Shatkin.
Sylvia, played by Georgia X. Lifsher.
Esa, played by Olga Merediz.
Like Sunday, Like Rain is a 2014 American drama film written and
directed by Frank Whaley, and distributed by Monterey Media.
The film stars Leighton Meester, Debra Messing, Billie Joe
Armstrong, and Julian Shatkin in his film debut.
The film follows a cello prodigy, Reggie, and his latest caretaker, Eleanor, as they
develop a friendship over the course of a summer in New York City.
It won at the Williamsburg Film Festival for Best
Feature and Best Director for Whaley himself.
Filming took place over 20 days in all five boroughs of New York City, New York.
Following a world premiere at the Raindance Film Festival in September 2014, and a US premiere at the Mill
Valley Film Festival in October 2014, the film was given a limited theatrical release in March 2015.
The film explores themes of new york city, friendship, au pair, prodigy.
The tone is emotional.